





# Full Stack Web Developer

## WHO AM I?

Python developer, with knowledge of APIs, mainly with Django Rest. Regular knowledge of Angular, with Bootstrap and Tailwind. I helped companies build web applications for e-commerce with more than 1 million users, knowledge of ERP functionalities and biotechnology software.

I have good adaptability in knowledge of business rules. I have great knowledge in SQL databases. In all the applications I worked on, agile methodologies such as Scrum, Kanban and Poker Planning were applied.

Python / Django / Git / REST APIs / Confluence / Jira / Google Cloud Platform (GCP) / Linux / SQL / Agile Methodologies / TypeScript / Angular

#### LANGUAGES

Português - Native

Inglês - Advanced / Technician

## **EXPERIENCE**

2022-01 - Current Full Stack Web Developer

Neoprospecta

Back-End Developer Django / Django Rest Framework with TDD and Unit Testing in software for biotechnology solutions. Development of features and maintenance in Angular.

Bitbucket / Confluence / Jira / Web Crawling / Google Cloud Platform (GCP) / Linux / PostgreSQL / Agile Methodologies / REST APIs / Python / Django REST Framework / TypeScript / Django / Bootstrap / AngularJS / Angular

2022-10 - 2023-10 **Backend Web Developer** 

Atar B2B

Back-End Developer Django / Django Rest Framework with TDD and Unit Testing in software for biotechnology solutions. Development of features and maintenance in Angular.

Github / Confluence / Jira / Web Crawling / Google Cloud Platform (GCP) / Linux / Docker / Agile Methodologies / REST APIs / Python / Architecture / AngularJS / FastAPI

2019-08 – 2022-01 Full Stack Web Developer

Magazine Médic

Full Stack Web Developer Python / Django / JS / Firebird / PostgreSQL - E-commerce / Internal System Develop APIs, Front-End, Back-End with tests in TDD, Database Modeling, UX/UI and Data Analysis.

Bitbucket / Jira / Firebase / Financial Analysis / PostgreSQL / REST APIs / User Experience (UX) / Python / Django / Bootstrap / JavaScript

**2018-11 - 2019-08 Database Analyst and Support** 

IXCSoft

SQL database migrations with DBs from external telecommunications systems to own system. Maintenance in MySQL to ERP database.

Analytical Skills / Microsoft SQL Server / PostgreSQL / Strategic Planning / Customer Service / SQL / MySQL / Firebird

2018-01 - 2018-11 Full Stack Web Developer Internship

Federal University of Fronteira Sul

Full Stack Web Python/Plone Developer - Institutional Site.
Plone / NoSQL / Python / Bootstrap / HTML5

### **EDUCATION**

2015 – 2018 Bachelor's Degree in Computer Science UFFS - Federal University of Fronteira Sul

Graduate

2019 – 2020 Systems Analysis, Design and Management UNOPAR - Universidade Norte do Paraná

Postgraduate

2020 – 2021	<b>Engenharia de Software</b> Postgraduate	Faculdade FAEL
2020 - 2021	<b>UX Design e Learning Experience</b> Postgraduate	Instituto de Desenho Instrucional
2021 - 2021	<b>Cloud Computing Projects</b> Postgraduate	Descomplica
2021 - 2021	<b>LGPD</b> Postgraduate	Faculdade Legale
2022 - 2023	<b>Technologies for Professional Education</b> Postgraduate	IFSC - Federal Institute of Santa Catarina
2021 - 2021	Accounting Technical Education	FASPEC